<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xml:base="https://2024.djangocon.us">
  <title>DjangoCon US 2024</title>
  <subtitle>Official conference news</subtitle>
  <link href="https://2024.djangocon.us/feed" rel="self"/>
  <link href="https://2024.djangocon.us" rel="alternate"/>

  <updated
    >2024-08-16T18:25:39Z</updated
  >
  <id>https://2024.djangocon.us</id>
  <author>
    <name>DjangoCon US Team</name>
    <email>hello@djangocon.us</email>
  </author>
    
    <entry>
      <title>A First-Timer's Guide to Navigating America</title>
      <link href="https://2024.djangocon.us/news/guide-to-america/" />
      <updated>2024-08-16T18:25:39Z</updated>
      <id>https://2024.djangocon.us/news/guide-to-america/</id>
      <content xml:lang="en" type="html"
        >&lt;p&gt;For many first-time attendees from abroad, DjangoCon US represents the first time for people entering the United States.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Before you can get into the USA, though, you may need a visa. Check our &lt;a href=&#34;/visas/&#34;&gt;Visa Support&lt;/a&gt; page for details and organizer Benedict Kofi Amofah&#39;s excellent &lt;a href=&#34;https://iamdreamo.medium.com/a-first-timers-guide-to-attending-tech-conferences-in-the-usa-visa-prep-and-beyond-e2e121db15df&#34;&gt;blog post&lt;/a&gt; on the visa preparation process.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Here&#39;s a quick guide to navigating life in the United States as a newcomer:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;payments&#34; tabindex=&#34;-1&#34;&gt;Payments&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Almost every venue nowadays takes Visa, MasterCard, American Express, and usually Discover. Make sure you notify your bank before you are traveling that you are going to the United States so you don&#39;t set off any fraud alerts. In the US, this requires calling the customer service number printed on the back of the card, but overseas banks may differ.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;When making payments, some card machines will give you the option to pay in USD or your home country; generally your bank will give you a more favorable exchange rate (even after conversion fees) than the merchant, so you should probably pick USD.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;carrying-cash&#34; tabindex=&#34;-1&#34;&gt;Carrying Cash&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;However, credit card machine failures do happen, so it&#39;s a good idea to carry a small bit of cash just in case. You will typically get better exchange rates at ATMs over airport currency exchange shops.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Many taxis will not have working card readers, so having cash for this is a must!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Most but not all vending machines will take cards and NFC payments (e.g. Apple Pay and Google Pay), so it&#39;s useful to have a few small bills ($1 is a paper note in the US, unlike most countries) just in case.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;mobile-phones&#34; tabindex=&#34;-1&#34;&gt;Mobile Phones&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The United States has 3 main wireless telecommunications providers: Verizon, AT&amp;amp;T, and T-Mobile. Now that Verizon has retired its 3G service, you should be able to bring nearly any phone that supports Voice over LTE (all 5G phones automatically do) and have it work in the US via roaming. However, that can be super expensive depending on your plan back home.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you want to get a temporary US plan, you have numerous options. The big three carriers are all post-paid, typically requiring long contract terms which make them unsuitable for a quick visit. However, there are numerous providers called MVNOs (mobile virtual network operators) that offer prepaid service, including:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Boost Mobile&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Cricket&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Visible&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Google Fi&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Tracfone&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Mint Mobile&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Many of these are able to offer a &amp;quot;bring your own phone&amp;quot; plan where you would have to get a SIM card, likely having it shipped to your hotel and then doing the swap yourself after you land in the US. You may also be able to find shops in the airport once you arrive in the US while you wait to board your final flight to RDU (Raleigh-Durham Airport) that offer SIM cards. Check the directory of your connecting airport for more information.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Alternatively, you can get an eSIM that you activate upon arrival. If your phone supports both an eSIM and a physical SIM, you can keep your normal phone number for receiving calls and use the eSIM for mobile data in the US. A few common providers are:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Airalo&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Holafly&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Nomad&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;aloSIM&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Jetpac&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Doing some internet searches (or asking your friends) might yield some handy discount codes, too.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;sales-tax&#34; tabindex=&#34;-1&#34;&gt;Sales Tax&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Many countries have some form of value added tax or goods and services tax rolled into the retail price that you pay, so a bottle of water that&#39;s listed as costing $2 is exactly what you  pay. In the US, this is very much &lt;em&gt;not&lt;/em&gt; the case. Instead, each state charges its own sales tax, and in many states, counties and municipalities add their own tax on top of that. Some places charge different tax rates for different classes of goods, such as a discount for food.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In Durham County, NC, the sales tax is a flat 7.5%. The city of Durham does not add its own sales tax. For example, you will pay $2.15 for the previous hypothetical $2 bottle of water.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;tipping&#34; tabindex=&#34;-1&#34;&gt;Tipping&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Tipping (gratuities) in the United States is rampant. Here&#39;s a rough idea of how much you&#39;ll be expected to add on top of your bill:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Restaurants: 20% for everything except for the big-name fast food restaurants (e.g. McDonald&#39;s, Wendy&#39;s, Burger King)
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Even some self-serve kiosk ordering places will try to ask for a tip! This money will theoretically go to the staff preparing and/or delivering your food, but it definitely feels odd.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Coffee shops: $1-2 per cup of coffee&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Bars: $1-2 per beer/glass of wine, $2-4 per cocktail, 20% on bottles of wine&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Rideshare and taxis: 20%&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Hotel room cleaning: ~$5/day (leave it on your pillow, weirdly)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Hotel valet parking: ~$3 per time they retrieve your car&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;transportation%2C-or-getting-from-the-airport-to-the-hotel&#34; tabindex=&#34;-1&#34;&gt;Transportation, or Getting from the Airport to the Hotel&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;There are 3 ways to get from the RDU airport to the Marriott:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Rideshare apps (Lyft and Uber generally have nationwide coverage; which you use is largely up to you) will generally get you where you need to go. It&#39;s about a $20-25 ride (plus tip) from the hotel to the airport in the absence of surge pricing. You&#39;ll pay using your phone. Use the app to find out where to get picked up. The ride should take about 20-25 minutes once you&#39;re in the car.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Traditional taxis may be hailed on the curb outside the airport. Follow signs for Ground Transportation and then try to wave down a cab that&#39;s going by. Fares will typically be a little more expensive ($30-35 perhaps plus tip), but licensing is stricter. Much like an Uber/Lyft, the trip should take about 20-25 minutes.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Durham is part of the &lt;a href=&#34;https://gotriangle.org&#34;&gt;GoTriangle&lt;/a&gt; Bus System that covers the Research Triangle. Fares are $2.50 per trip, and the route from the airport to the hotel takes approximately an hour including 10-minute walks on each end of the journey. Use the &lt;a href=&#34;https://gotriangle.org/UMO&#34;&gt;Umo&lt;/a&gt; app to make payments through your phone.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;identification%2Fpurchasing-alcohol&#34; tabindex=&#34;-1&#34;&gt;Identification/Purchasing Alcohol&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;To purchase alcohol or enter places that predominantly serve alcohol, there&#39;s a very good chance you&#39;ll be required to present identification. You &lt;em&gt;may&lt;/em&gt; be able to get away with a national ID card, but your safest option is your passport. It needs to be the original; photocopies are not accepted.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;recycling&#34; tabindex=&#34;-1&#34;&gt;Recycling&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Recycling is extremely hit or miss in public facilities. Airports typically have some sort of recycling setup, and urban cores typically have recycling for plastic types #1 or #2 and aluminum cans and not much else.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;All other waste goes into a single trash stream.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;public-restrooms&#34; tabindex=&#34;-1&#34;&gt;Public Restrooms&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Unlike many European cities, you&#39;re not likely to find public paid toilets. If you find yourself in need of a trip to the restroom while out in public, you have a few options:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Public parks typically have restrooms open to the public&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Visit a retail establishment (grocery store, convenience store, coffee shop, etc.) and buy something&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Public libraries&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;flying-home&#34; tabindex=&#34;-1&#34;&gt;Flying Home&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;When returning home, you&#39;ll want to plan on arriving at RDU airport two hours before your departure time. Odds are you will clear security with plenty of time to spare, but in the event of another CrowdStrike-class outage, it&#39;s better to have time on your side.&lt;/p&gt;
</content
      >
    </entry>
    
    <entry>
      <title>Announcing Our Keynotes: Natalia Bidart</title>
      <link href="https://2024.djangocon.us/news/introducing-keynote-natalia-bidart/" />
      <updated>2024-08-16T18:25:39Z</updated>
      <id>https://2024.djangocon.us/news/introducing-keynote-natalia-bidart/</id>
      <content xml:lang="en" type="html"
        >&lt;h3 id=&#34;we&#39;re-honored-to-announce-our-third-keynote-speaker-for-djangocon-us-2024-and-django-fellow%3A-natalia-bidart&#34; tabindex=&#34;-1&#34;&gt;We&#39;re honored to announce our third keynote speaker for DjangoCon US 2024 and Django Fellow: Natalia Bidart&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We had the opportunity to sit down with Natalia and ask a few questions about her work, upcoming talk, and what she is looking forward to at DjangoCon US 2024.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;can-you-tell-us-how-you-use-django-is-our-go-to-question%2C-but-how-has-your-time-as-a-django-fellow-been-so-far%3F&#34; tabindex=&#34;-1&#34;&gt;Can you tell us how you use Django is our go to question, but how has your time as a Django Fellow been so far?&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I joined April last year. So it&#39;s been a year and four months, that I&#39;ve been a fellow, and it has been great, very challenging in that prior to to being a fellow, I wasn&#39;t that involved in contributing to Django, so there was an initial period when everything was new to me, and I mean everything, like how to do things, reading the docs, when it comes to contributing, building PRs, reviewing PRs, triage and tickets and getting used to formats and guidelines for the code, the commit messages, the bulk triage flows in different stages. So, it was definitely a non trivial period and non trivial adaptation to get used to. At times I felt a little bit inadequate for the position, so I tried to shift my focus to getting to know the community and the different ways of doing things. I tried to put my energy to where I thought it could provide the most value, which was around engaging with the community and trying to ease different interactions and attend to those PRs. So, yes it has been a very challenging process, but I have also learned a lot, and I am honored to be a Django fellow.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;can-you-give-us-a-teaser-about-what-your-talk-is-about%3F&#34; tabindex=&#34;-1&#34;&gt;Can you give us a teaser about what your talk is about?&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I&#39;d like to talk about the Django Fellowship program, which I&#39;m a part of. This program is crucial for maintaining Django’s current status as a secure, robust, and progressive framework. One of the key reasons to donate to the Django Software Foundation (DSF) is that a significant portion of donations goes directly to funding this Fellowship.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Fellows play an essential role in managing and unifying the diverse contributions that come from the community. We ensure consistency, maintain high standards, and safeguard the overall quality of Django. You can think of our role as being the housekeepers of Django, putting up guardrails to maintain the framework&#39;s integrity.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It’s important to raise awareness about the Fellowship, not just for fundraising, but also because many people, even those who use Django daily, aren’t fully aware of what the program entails. When I was appointed a Fellow, I found myself explaining what the Django Fellowship is to my peers, some of whom teased, &amp;quot;Is it something like the Fellowship of the Ring?&amp;quot;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;what-are-you-most-looking-forward-to-at-djangocon-us-2024%3F&#34; tabindex=&#34;-1&#34;&gt;What are you most looking forward to at DjangoCon US 2024?&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This will be my third DjangoCon. Last year at DjangoCon US 2023 was my first, and I also attended DjangoCon Europe earlier this year. What&#39;s exciting about this DjangoCon US is that both Sarah Boyce and I, the current Django Fellows, will be there together for the first time. Last year Marius the other Fellow, couldn&#39;t attend, and Sarah couldn&#39;t make it to DjangoCon Europe because she had an important personal event. So, having both of us there is something I&#39;m really looking forward to.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This time around, I feel more prepared and less nervous. Last year, I was anxious and had a lot of questions about how things would work. Now that I have some answers and more experience, I hope to enjoy the conference even more. If I can get my talk ready on time, I think I’ll be able to relax and fully immerse myself in the event. Last year was more intense for me because it was my first DjangoCon as a Fellow, and I wasn&#39;t sure what to expect or what people expected from me.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;what-are-your-favorite-topics-at-conferences%3F&#34; tabindex=&#34;-1&#34;&gt;What are your favorite topics at conferences?&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I enjoy non-technical topics, and I find that technical topics can be tackled effectively through a computer. Since they are often algorithmic or complex, I can engage with them directly at the keyboard. However, when it comes to topics like inclusion, I believe they are much more nuanced and multifaceted. These discussions benefit greatly from a conference setting where the environment is more fluid, and you can pick up on non-verbal cues like gestures and tones of voice, which are crucial for understanding the full context.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I think it&#39;s essential to acknowledge that Django’s progress depends on the strength and diversity of its community. You can&#39;t afford to be selective about who is welcome in the community based on arbitrary criteria. Of course, there are standards of conduct that everyone should adhere to, and that’s necessary for maintaining a healthy and inclusive environment. But beyond that, openness and inclusivity are vital for the community to thrive.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;what-do-you-like-to-do-outside-of-your-normal-work-day%3F&#34; tabindex=&#34;-1&#34;&gt;What do you like to do outside of your normal work day?&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As a parent most of my time goes into my child. I really love power tools, whatever it is, to grab a tool and plug it in and do something with that! I really like woodwork, yoga, and doing some gardening.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;are-you-okay-with-people-asking-you-more-later%3F&#34; tabindex=&#34;-1&#34;&gt;Are you okay with people asking you more later?&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I&#39;m totally fine with questions, yes!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Be sure to follow &lt;a href=&#34;https://fosstodon.org/@nessita&#34;&gt;Natalia&lt;/a&gt; on Mastodon!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We can&#39;t wait to hear Natalia&#39;s keynote at DjangoCon US 2024! Stay tuned for more keynote announcements and the full schedule. If you haven’t purchased your ticket yet, &lt;a href=&#34;https://ti.to/defna/djangocon-us-2024&#34;&gt;they’re still on sale&lt;/a&gt;. We hope to see you in Durham! 🐂&lt;/p&gt;
</content
      >
    </entry>
    
    <entry>
      <title>Build something cool with Django at DjangoCon US!</title>
      <link href="https://2024.djangocon.us/news/participate-in-djangocon-us-hackathon/" />
      <updated>2024-08-16T18:25:39Z</updated>
      <id>https://2024.djangocon.us/news/participate-in-djangocon-us-hackathon/</id>
      <content xml:lang="en" type="html"
        >&lt;p&gt;This year DjangoCon US will feature a hackathon. It&#39;s open to developers of all experience levels. You&#39;re welcome to take part as an individual or within a group. There is limited availability and early registration is requested.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you&#39;re interested in participating, please see the &lt;a href=&#34;/hackathon/&#34;&gt;Hackathon page&lt;/a&gt; for more details.&lt;/p&gt;
</content
      >
    </entry>
    
    <entry>
      <title>Volunteer at DjangoCon US: An Opportunity to Give Back and Grow</title>
      <link href="https://2024.djangocon.us/news/volunteer-opportunities/" />
      <updated>2024-08-16T18:25:39Z</updated>
      <id>https://2024.djangocon.us/news/volunteer-opportunities/</id>
      <content xml:lang="en" type="html"
        >&lt;p&gt;DjangoCon US is a premier event for the Django community, and it wouldn&#39;t be possible without the invaluable contributions of our volunteers. As a co-chair of the Volunteer program, I can attest to the immense impact that our volunteers have on the success of this conference.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;why-should-you-volunteer%3F&#34; tabindex=&#34;-1&#34;&gt;Why Should You Volunteer?&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I know you&#39;re already busy, but hear me out – volunteering at DjangoCon US is an opportunity you don&#39;t want to miss. Here&#39;s why:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Contribute:&lt;/strong&gt; When you volunteer, you help the community to grow and give feedback to Django as a product and ecosystem. This is your opportunity to have a real impact and help the tech and the people you love.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Level up:&lt;/strong&gt; Volunteering at a conference like this is a wonderful experience where you can gain a lot of knowledge and new skills. You will acquire a range of new skills: from organizing events, rallying the troops, and problem-solving. Nah, these are the types of skill sets that do you good in real life and even professionally.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Get Networking:&lt;/strong&gt; Volunteers will be working alongside Django engineers from around the globe, including some of the most experienced and passionate Django contributors and consultants—such a valuable chance to network, collaborate on projects, and build lasting friendships within the community.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;/assets/img/blog/health-and-safety-desk.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;Health and safey desk&#34;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;what-can-you-expect-as-a-volunteer%3F&#34; tabindex=&#34;-1&#34;&gt;What Can You Expect as a Volunteer?&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Flexible Schedules:&lt;/strong&gt; We know you&#39;ve got a lot going on, so we&#39;re committed to creating volunteer schedules that accommodate your availability. You can choose to volunteer for a few hours, a day, or the entire conference – whatever works best for you.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Varied Roles:&lt;/strong&gt; We have a wide range of volunteer positions available, from registration desk assistance to session monitoring, and health and safety check-in.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Training and Support:&lt;/strong&gt; Don&#39;t worry, you won&#39;t be thrown in the deep end. As a volunteer, you&#39;ll receive comprehensive training and support to make sure you&#39;re well-equipped to handle your assigned tasks. Our experienced team will guide you every step of the way.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;/assets/img/blog/volunteers-at-djangocon.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;Volunteers at DjangoCon US&#34;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;online-volunteers&#34; tabindex=&#34;-1&#34;&gt;Online Volunteers&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;What if you can’t be there in person? Don’t worry, we have volunteer opportunities online as well! We need online moderators to encourage discussion in the public chat and answer questions about the online platform as they come up.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;/assets/img/blog/catherine-registration-desk.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;Catherine Holmes at registration desk&#34;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;So, what do you say? Ready to join us and be a part of something truly special? Head over to our &lt;a href=&#34;https://docs.google.com/spreadsheets/d/1NXwhDPhl5hCBTXgkMQffSPiLU70wTRGV8Ruu8OoUJkY/edit?gid=2088259231#gid=2088259231&#34;&gt;volunteer signup page&lt;/a&gt; to sign up or learn more. We can&#39;t wait to have you on the team!&lt;/p&gt;
</content
      >
    </entry>
    
    <entry>
      <title>Childcare During DjangoCon US</title>
      <link href="https://2024.djangocon.us/news/childcare-during-djangocon/" />
      <updated>2024-08-16T18:25:39Z</updated>
      <id>https://2024.djangocon.us/news/childcare-during-djangocon/</id>
      <content xml:lang="en" type="html"
        >&lt;p&gt;Childcare at DjangoCon US and tech conferences more generally is an important factor that helps folks attend who otherwise may not be able to. We want to make sure that parents feel welcome bringing their children to DjangoCon US and that the availability of childcare is not a barrier to attending.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;To assist with that, DjangoCon US will reimburse you for childcare during the conference (up to $150 per day) with a receipt.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;For nursing parents, we will provide a clean, comfortable, and private lactation space at the conference venue. The room will have a small refrigerator to store pumped milk, labeling supplies, and antibacterial wipes.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Please contact us at &lt;a href=&#34;mailto:hello@defna.org&#34;&gt;hello@defna.org&lt;/a&gt; if you are interested in utilizing DjangoCon US’s child care reimbursement or lactation space services.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We have also collected information on a few local childcare providers:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://kidzkampdropin.com/&#34;&gt;Kidz Kamp Drop-in&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;12 mo - 12 yr&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;$225 for 25 hrs
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;See other pricing options &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.kidzkampdropin.com/copy-of-our-prices-1&#34;&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.kreativekidznc.com/dropin&#34;&gt;Kreative Kidz NC&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;8 hr stay pass $75/child + $50/sibling
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;See other pricing options &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.kreativekidznc.com/dropin-pricing&#34;&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.dropinkidscare.org/&#34;&gt;Courtney&#39;s Drop-in Kids Care&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;6 mo - 12 yr&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;$12/hr and other packages available
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;See other pricing options &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.dropinkidscare.org/packages-and-pricing&#34;&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;This &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.childcareservices.org/families/find-child-care/&#34;&gt;referral organization&lt;/a&gt; may be worth a shot if you want to look into other options&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We look forward to seeing you -- and your kids -- soon in Durham!&lt;/p&gt;
</content
      >
    </entry>
    
    <entry>
      <title>Announcing Our Keynotes: Mario Munoz</title>
      <link href="https://2024.djangocon.us/news/introducing-keynote-mario-munoz/" />
      <updated>2024-08-16T18:25:39Z</updated>
      <id>https://2024.djangocon.us/news/introducing-keynote-mario-munoz/</id>
      <content xml:lang="en" type="html"
        >&lt;h3 id=&#34;we&#39;re-honored-to-announce-our-second-keynote-speaker-for-djangocon-us-2024%3A-mario-munoz!&#34; tabindex=&#34;-1&#34;&gt;We&#39;re honored to announce our second keynote speaker for DjangoCon US 2024: Mario Munoz!&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We had the opportunity to sit down with Mario and ask him a few questions about his work, his upcoming talk, and what he&#39;s looking forward to at DjangoCon US 2024.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;can-you-tell-us-how-you-use-django%3F&#34; tabindex=&#34;-1&#34;&gt;Can you tell us how you use Django?&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;When preparing my first talk on &lt;a href=&#34;https://2022.djangocon.us/talks/why-i-didn-t-start-with-django/&#34;&gt;&amp;quot;Why I Didn&#39;t Start With Django&amp;quot;&lt;/a&gt;, I thought I should at least build a Django app before getting into it... As a result, I built an app to hold my presentation slides (also using reveal.js), and ever since, I&#39;ve continued using it for the past two years.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;can-you-give-us-a-teaser-about-what-your-talk-is-about%3F&#34; tabindex=&#34;-1&#34;&gt;Can you give us a teaser about what your talk is about?&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I am very interested in the intersection of people and technology. What role does community have in our technological journey? How do we see ourselves within the context of a &amp;quot;technical&amp;quot; community?  At a recent conference (North Bay Python), &lt;a href=&#34;https://pretalx.northbaypython.org/nbpy-2024/talk/X7ZZPP/&#34;&gt;I spoke about building bridges between communities&lt;/a&gt;. My talk at DjangoCon US will be an extension of this. My current working title is &amp;quot;How to be a developer, and other lies we tell ourselves.&amp;quot; We&#39;ll be going through a journey that brings us in and out of different mindsets as developers, and what role community plays in all of this. As many of my talks, I often have many biographical/personal/meta examples...&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;what-are-you-most-looking-forward-to-at-djangocon-us-2024%3F&#34; tabindex=&#34;-1&#34;&gt;What are you most looking forward to at DjangoCon US 2024?&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I am most excited about engaging with the community. I am currently involved in the Djangonaut Space program and look forward to seeing fellow Djangonauts there. I&#39;ve also seen that the talks have been posted, and some of them look fantastic. I&#39;m interested in all things hypermedia, so definitely will be catching those HTMX-related talks.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;what-are-your-favorite-topics-at-conferences%3F&#34; tabindex=&#34;-1&#34;&gt;What are your favorite topics at conferences?&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As mentioned, I&#39;m excited about the hypermedia. But I always like hearing about broad topics, such as &lt;a href=&#34;/talks/django-user-model-past-present-and-future/&#34;&gt;the past, present, and future of Django&#39;s User Model talk by Will&lt;/a&gt;, or &lt;a href=&#34;/talks/if-we-had-1000000-what-could-the-dsf-do-with-4x-its-budget/&#34;&gt;Jacob&#39;s talk on what the DSF could accomplish with 4x the budget&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;how-do-you-view-the-connections-made-at-conferences%3F&#34; tabindex=&#34;-1&#34;&gt;How do you view the connections made at conferences?&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The connections we make are invaluable. As an introvert, like many of us, I seek meaningful and strong connections. The Django community, in particular, has been a welcoming space for these interactions.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;can-you-tell-us-about-your-career-journey%3F&#34; tabindex=&#34;-1&#34;&gt;Can you tell us about your career journey?&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I started my career in payroll and then moved to an HR analyst role, providing IT-related support. It was through networking that I met people who helped me transition into engineering. I met some key contacts at PyCon US.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;how-did-you-approach-your-career-growth%3F&#34; tabindex=&#34;-1&#34;&gt;How did you approach your career growth?&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I purposely leaned into areas where I wasn’t as strong, getting out there and trying to speak. It’s a long-term investment, and it takes time to get there. Purposefully plugging into the community and focusing on what you can do with code, whether you&#39;re a newcomer or experienced, is crucial. Learning not to gatekeep is also important.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;when-did-you-start-speaking-at-conferences%2C-and-what-has-your-experience-been-like%3F&#34; tabindex=&#34;-1&#34;&gt;When did you start speaking at conferences, and what has your experience been like?&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I started speaking in 2022, giving talks at PyCon US and PyOhio. I&#39;ve done tutorials and talks, and it&#39;s been an incredible experience that has helped me grow both personally and professionally.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;what-do-you-like-to-do-outside-of-your-normal-work-day%3F&#34; tabindex=&#34;-1&#34;&gt;What do you like to do outside of your normal work day?&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Beach days with the family are always fun, or adventuring in a new/unknown hiking area. And, well, I have a blog called &lt;a href=&#34;https://pythonbynight.com/&#34;&gt;Python By Night&lt;/a&gt;, so that kind of speaks for itself.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;are-you-ok-with-people-asking-you-more-later%3F&#34; tabindex=&#34;-1&#34;&gt;Are you ok with people asking you more later?&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Yes!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Be sure to follow &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.linkedin.com/in/mario-a-munoz/&#34;&gt;Mario&lt;/a&gt; on LinkedIn!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We can&#39;t wait to hear Mario&#39;s keynote at DjangoCon US 2024! Stay tuned for more keynote announcements and the full schedule. If you haven’t purchased your ticket yet, &lt;a href=&#34;https://ti.to/defna/djangocon-us-2024&#34;&gt;they’re still on sale&lt;/a&gt;. We hope to see you in Durham! 🐂&lt;/p&gt;
</content
      >
    </entry>
    
    <entry>
      <title>Getting to know folks: A pre-conference interview</title>
      <link href="https://2024.djangocon.us/news/getting-to-know-folks/" />
      <updated>2024-08-16T18:25:39Z</updated>
      <id>https://2024.djangocon.us/news/getting-to-know-folks/</id>
      <content xml:lang="en" type="html"
        >&lt;p&gt;Hello Djangonauts!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;DjangoCon US 🐂 is coming up, and our excitement is building. There isn&#39;t any news to share today, but we have something just as great!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We’re spending a little time getting to know people who will be attending DjangoCon US this September. We asked various people who have different connections and experiences with the Django community.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.linkedin.com/in/amandasavluchinske/&#34;&gt;Amanda Savluchinske&lt;/a&gt; is a first-time speaker and attendee at DjangoCon US&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.programmingmylife.com/&#34;&gt;Andrew Mshar&lt;/a&gt; is a first-time organizer&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.linkedin.com/in/carolganz/&#34;&gt;Carol Ganz&lt;/a&gt; is a board member of DEFNA and DjangoCon US organizer&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://dev.to/chrisachinga&#34;&gt;Chris Achinga&lt;/a&gt; is a first-time attendee&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://kojoidrissa.com/&#34;&gt;Kojo Idrissa&lt;/a&gt; is a long-time attendee, speaker and organizer of DjangoCon US&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;So let’s get to meeting them!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Note, the remainder of the post switches to first person from the perspective of Tim,&lt;/em&gt; &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.defna.org/&#34;&gt;&lt;em&gt;DEFNA&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt; &lt;em&gt;secretary and DjangoCon US 2024 communications co-chair.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Interviewer Tim&lt;/strong&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Hi folks, thanks for agreeing to this. Let’s start with having you tell us a little about yourself and your connection to the Django community.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Amanda&lt;/strong&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I’m a PM, and I love what I do. I also still enjoy coding. I knew I wanted some kind of hybrid career even before getting into university, when I decided to major in Business Administration. Nowadays, I’m specializing in Software Engineering, mostly to formalize the knowledge I’ve acquired during my years as a software engineer, as well as cover some gaps.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I started out my journey in Django in 2017, when I attended a &lt;a href=&#34;https://djangogirls.org&#34;&gt;Django Girls&lt;/a&gt; workshop in my hometown. In 2018, I organized one myself. It was through that first workshop that I got my internship as a software engineer, and I quickly learned to love Python, and especially Django. Throughout this six-seven year span, I also got the opportunity to speak at some Python/Django conferences, starting out at local ones, then regional, national (&lt;a href=&#34;https://pythonbrasil.org.br&#34;&gt;Python Brasil&lt;/a&gt;) and international (&lt;a href=&#34;https://djangocon.eu&#34;&gt;DjangoCon Europe&lt;/a&gt;). Even though speaking is an experience that is always a little scary to me, the community has always been welcoming and warm, and that keeps me going.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Andrew&lt;/strong&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I&#39;m a software developer who uses Django professionally, both at my day job and for a side project. I blog (not regularly) about technologies that I use, which includes Django. I&#39;ve attended (and very much enjoyed) the last two DjangoCon US events.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Carol&lt;/strong&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I am an Account Manager at Six Feet Up, and we use Django for a lot of projects. As an organization, we believe in giving back to the open-source community. So, after meeting DEFNA co-founder Jeff Triplett at our event, the &lt;a href=&#34;https://pythonwebconf.com&#34;&gt;Python Web Conference&lt;/a&gt;, and talking about the best way to contribute to the Django community. Based on his input, I ran for the DEFNA board and was elected. Since then, I have helped organize 4 DjangoCon US conferences.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Chris&lt;/strong&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;My first Django event was the &lt;a href=&#34;https://2023.djangocon.africa/&#34;&gt;DjangoCon Africa&lt;/a&gt;, and I was exposed to the global Django community that I didn&#39;t know existed even here in Kenya. Since then, I have been actively participating in activities related to Django and the community, and also applying to speak and attend a few Django/Python conferences.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Kojo&lt;/strong&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I&#39;ve been a DCUS organizer since 2016, and I&#39;ve spoken a few times (2015, 2017, and a panel one of the San Diego years).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Interviewer Tim&lt;/strong&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Fantastic! Can you please tell us what you’re looking forward to at DjangoCon US 2024?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Amanda&lt;/strong&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It’s going to be my first in-person international conference. When I &lt;a href=&#34;https://2021.djangocon.eu/cfp/talk/ECY3JD/index.html&#34;&gt;spoke at DjangoCon Europe&lt;/a&gt;, that was online, so I didn’t get to experience a lot of the fun and connection in-person conferences offer. I’m really looking forward to the talks as well, there are incredible topics there from what I’ve seen.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Andrew&lt;/strong&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Catching up with other members of the community in person!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Carol&lt;/strong&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Meeting new people and learning about new ways the community is growing.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Chris&lt;/strong&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I really learned a lot from last year&#39;s event, although I did not attend. By following live updates on X and also the &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.youtube.com/c/DjangoConUS&#34;&gt;uploaded sessions on YouTube&lt;/a&gt;, my development skills have been better, and I am more open to giving and sharing my ideas in various communities&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Kojo&lt;/strong&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Seeing folks I don&#39;t get to see often and being able to engage more with people.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Interviewer Tim&lt;/strong&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;What country are you traveling from?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Amanda&lt;/strong&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Portugal, but I’m from Brazil.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Andrew&lt;/strong&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;USA&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Carol&lt;/strong&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;United States&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Chris&lt;/strong&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Kenya (Not attending, but would love to participate online)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Kojo&lt;/strong&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;USA&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Interviewer Tim&lt;/strong&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;What made you decide to attend/speak/organize this year?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Amanda&lt;/strong&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Through work, I ended up presenting an online talk at Women Who Code NYC. It was a great experience, and the attendees seemed to enjoy and engage with the content. When DjangoCon US announced their CFP, I was like well, I have a talk that could also be interesting to the Django community, so why not? I didn’t have high expectations of it getting approved, so it was a great surprise. I had only submitted to DCUS’ CFP once before, but speaking at the conference has always been an interest of mine.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Andrew&lt;/strong&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I am attending because attending the last two years has been great. I&#39;m organizing because I enjoyed the conference so much that I wanted to help out.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Carol&lt;/strong&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I really enjoy working with this team of organizers. Everyone is so helpful, and it makes it so much easier to have an amazing conference when you have so many diverse contributors.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Chris&lt;/strong&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;To learn more, I also want to start looking for new opportunities in the Django ecosystem&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Kojo&lt;/strong&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I enjoy helping welcome people to our community.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Interviewer Tim&lt;/strong&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Is it possible to resonate with all of those answers? Because I do. Now, here’s my most controversial question. Are you a sticker or pin person?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Amanda&lt;/strong&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Pins!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Andrew&lt;/strong&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Stickers!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Carol&lt;/strong&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Stickers!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Chris&lt;/strong&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Stickers!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Kojo&lt;/strong&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Stickers!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Interviewer Tim&lt;/strong&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Thank you, Amanda, for justifying that question, I knew there were more of us out there!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I’m a relatively new conference-goer myself. So one thing I’m curious about are other people’s tips and tricks for attending conferences. But first, does anyone have a tip/trick they’d like to know more about?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Amanda&lt;/strong&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I’d love a tip on how to get to know people during breaks!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Kojo&lt;/strong&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you needed to get support from your organization/company to attend DCUS, did you need to convince them? If so, how&#39;d you do it? What arguments did you lay out? This is in contrast to a situation where you have an Education/Training budget of $X and no one really cares WHAT you use it on, so long as you don&#39;t exceed it.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Interviewer Tim&lt;/strong&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I can definitely relate to wanting to have an idea of how to meet people at the conference. And getting support from your job to attend a conference can be a real game-changer when the conference isn’t local. If folks have suggestions for either of these, please share them on social media with the #DjangoConUS hashtag or tag us in the message.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Does anyone have their own tips or tricks for attending a conference?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Andrew&lt;/strong&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Getting the most out of your time at the conference doesn&#39;t mean doing all of the things all of the time. Pace yourself. That might mean a nap, or just some quiet time at some point during the day to keep your energy up. Leave some slack in your schedule so you can be flexible and enjoy your time.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Carol&lt;/strong&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Sit with people you do not already know. You can hang out with people you already know any time.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Welcome others into your conversations. I tend to be an introvert, so it is nice to be able to just sit and listen to others when you are welcome at the table.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Volunteer to work at the welcome desk to get to meet lots of new people. That’s how I met Tim.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Talk slowly and clearly. English is not everyone&#39;s first language.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Chris&lt;/strong&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Be a good audience. A lot of time and thought was put into selecting speakers. Speakers have spent valuable time researching on the topics to deliver amazing content, the best reward for the speakers and organizers is to be a great audience.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Kojo&lt;/strong&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If there&#39;s a talk on a topic or given by someone where you&#39;d want to ask them a question, Prioritize Attending That Talk. It&#39;s a rare opportunity to ask your direct question. Otherwise, prioritize in-person interaction. Those conversations and meetings are ALSO rare.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Interviewer Tim&lt;/strong&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Thank you everyone, these insights are incredibly valuable and will help everyone be a part of a fantastic event.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;My last question is again a two part-er. I’d like to know what one word best describes DjangoCon US. Or if you haven’t attended, what word best describes your emotions leading up to it?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Amanda&lt;/strong&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Anticipation&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Andrew&lt;/strong&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Community.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Carol&lt;/strong&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Friendly&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Chris&lt;/strong&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I haven&#39;t had the chance to attend DjangoCon US, but from the information I see everywhere on the internet:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Ajab! (Swahili word for Amazing)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Kojo&lt;/strong&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Describe DCUS: Enriching&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Emotions leading up to DCUS: Conflicted (balancing responsibilities with anticipation)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Interviewer Tim&lt;/strong&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I absolutely love these answers. I second each of them, but if someone had put palm-sweat-inducing down, that would be my winner.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Thank you all for spending your time and energy on this, the event, your talks and the Django community as a whole. I’m looking forward to seeing you all in September and you Chris, hopefully at a DjangoCon US in the future!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;For everyone else, if this has excited you about DjangoCon US 🐂, &lt;a href=&#34;https://ti.to/defna/djangocon-us-2024&#34;&gt;buy your ticket today&lt;/a&gt;!&lt;/p&gt;
</content
      >
    </entry>
    
    <entry>
      <title>Announcing Our Keynotes: Sheena O'Connell</title>
      <link href="https://2024.djangocon.us/news/introducing-keynote-sheena-oconnell/" />
      <updated>2024-08-16T18:25:39Z</updated>
      <id>https://2024.djangocon.us/news/introducing-keynote-sheena-oconnell/</id>
      <content xml:lang="en" type="html"
        >&lt;h3 id=&#34;we&#39;re-honored-to-announce-our-first-keynote-speaker-for-djangocon-us-2024%3A-sheena-o&#39;connell!&#34; tabindex=&#34;-1&#34;&gt;We&#39;re honored to announce our first keynote speaker for DjangoCon US 2024: Sheena O&#39;Connell!&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We had the opportunity to sit down with Sheena and ask her a few questions about her work, her upcoming talk, and what she&#39;s looking forward to at DjangoCon US 2024.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;how-do-you-use-django%3F&#34; tabindex=&#34;-1&#34;&gt;How Do You Use Django?&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Currently, I use it at work. We have a learner management system built in Django. I spoke about it at DjangoCon US 2022. That project is still running, but it&#39;s changed a bit. We have moved away from a React-based frontend to something built with HTMX, and it&#39;s way nicer.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;can-you-give-us-a-teaser-about-your-upcoming-talk%3F&#34; tabindex=&#34;-1&#34;&gt;Can You Give Us a Teaser About Your Upcoming Talk?&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Software developers are often put in positions where they need to teach - this can be a part of their job (eg: onboarding the new human, explaining your stuff to non-technical humans, taking part in mentorship, actually being paid to teach) or through community events and volunteering. These teachers often are not trained in how to teach. And even those that don&#39;t teach others need to teach themselves. This is a learning career.&lt;br&gt;
My talk is about how to teach foundational code. So it&#39;s also about the science of learning. There are evidence-based methods that work, and common anti-patterns that set people back. Teaching well is an art and a science. My goal here is to set everyone in the audience up to be better teachers, it&#39;s a big goal for a talk, but I&#39;m sure I can light a few fires.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;what-are-you-most-looking-forward-to-at-djangocon-us-2024%3F&#34; tabindex=&#34;-1&#34;&gt;What Are You Most Looking Forward to at DjangoCon US 2024?&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The people! I enjoy the talks, and I&#39;ve benefited a lot from them, but the community is the thing that keeps making me want to come back.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;what-are-your-favorite-topics-at-conferences%3F&#34; tabindex=&#34;-1&#34;&gt;What Are Your Favorite Topics at Conferences?&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I like being introduced to things I can use and don&#39;t yet know about. For example, I&#39;ve found previous talks on HTMX and Playwright really useful. I use those tools now. I really like anything that is actionable. And I enjoy good stories and new ways of looking at things. If I can leave curious and inspired, then I&#39;m happy.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;have-you-presented-at-other-conferences%3F&#34; tabindex=&#34;-1&#34;&gt;Have You Presented at Other Conferences?&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I&#39;ve presented at many places since my first conference, including DjangoCon Africa, DjangoCon Europe, and local conferences like PyCon Namibia and PyCon South Africa. Recently, my work has shifted more towards teaching teachers rather than directly working on hard tech. This involves dealing with stakeholders and non-developers, which requires a lot of learning and adaptation.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;what-are-you-passionate-about%3F&#34; tabindex=&#34;-1&#34;&gt;What Are You Passionate About?&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I&#39;m heavily involved in building communities through new conferences and other initiatives. It&#39;s rewarding to see the impact, especially in smaller communities like PyCon Namibia. These efforts are life-changing for small communities. I have been thinking and planning ways to support tech education. I will be launching this soon, so please keep an eye out for it.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;what-do-you-like-to-do-outside-of-your-normal-workday%3F&#34; tabindex=&#34;-1&#34;&gt;What Do You Like to Do Outside of Your Normal Workday?&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Way too many things. I enjoy climbing quite a lot. I also have a &lt;a href=&#34;http://sheenaoc.com/&#34;&gt;blog&lt;/a&gt; where I mostly talk about tech education. I have been teaching myself to play guitar, but it&#39;s not always something I have time for.   I also love hiking, I do one or two multi-day hikes per year, I enjoy getting very far from civilization from time to time. Lastly, I always have some kind of side quest going on.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;are-you-open-to-people-reaching-out-later%3F&#34; tabindex=&#34;-1&#34;&gt;Are You Open to People Reaching Out Later?&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Yes, definitely!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Be sure to follow &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.linkedin.com/in/sheena-o-connell-0bb72527/&#34;&gt;Sheena&lt;/a&gt; on LinkedIn and check out her &lt;a href=&#34;http://sheenaoc.com/&#34;&gt;blog&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We can&#39;t wait to hear Sheena&#39;s keynote at DjangoCon US 2024! Stay tuned for more keynote announcements and the full schedule. If you haven’t purchased your ticket yet, &lt;a href=&#34;https://ti.to/defna/djangocon-us-2024&#34;&gt;they’re still on sale&lt;/a&gt;. We hope to see you in Durham! 🐂&lt;/p&gt;
</content
      >
    </entry>
    
    <entry>
      <title>The DjangoCon US 2024 schedule has been released!</title>
      <link href="https://2024.djangocon.us/news/announcing-schedule-dcus/" />
      <updated>2024-08-16T18:25:39Z</updated>
      <id>https://2024.djangocon.us/news/announcing-schedule-dcus/</id>
      <content xml:lang="en" type="html"
        >&lt;p&gt;We are beyond thrilled to unveil the 2024 DjangoCon US &lt;a href=&#34;/schedule/&#34;&gt;talk and tutorial lineup&lt;/a&gt;. We&#39;ll have six tutorials on Sunday, September 22, three days of talks on September 23-25, and two days of sprints on September 26-27.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We will have three keynote speakers which will be announced over the next several weeks. Stay tuned to our &lt;a href=&#34;https://fosstodon.org/@djangocon&#34;&gt;Mastodon&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href=&#34;/news/&#34;&gt;news feed&lt;/a&gt; for the announcements.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We have lots of great talks lined up, from talks about &lt;a href=&#34;/talks/error-culture/&#34;&gt;Error Culture&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&#34;/talks/troubleshooting-is-a-lifestyle/&#34;&gt;Troubleshooting&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&#34;/talks/django-the-web-framework-that-changed-my-life/&#34;&gt;Django: the web frameework that changed my life&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&#34;/talks/django-alpine-js-htmx-ups-downs/&#34;&gt;Django + Alpine.js + htmx Ups &amp;amp; Downs&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&#34;/talks/maps-with-django/&#34;&gt;Maps with Django&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&#34;/talks/how-to-design-and-implement-extensible-software-with-plugins/&#34;&gt;How to design and implement extensible software with plugins&lt;/a&gt; &lt;a href=&#34;/talks/fighting-homelessness-with-django/&#34;&gt;Fighting Homelessness with Django&lt;/a&gt;, and so much more!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Don&#39;t forget our awesome deep dive day, where we dig into things like &lt;a href=&#34;/talks/hidden-gems-of-django-5-x/&#34;&gt;Hidden gems of Django 5.x&lt;/a&gt; from new Django Fellow Sarah Boyce, &lt;a href=&#34;/talks/a-brief-history-of-django/&#34;&gt;A Brief History of Django&lt;/a&gt;, and learning more about &lt;a href=&#34;/talks/django-user-model-past-present-and-future/&#34;&gt;Django User Model: Past, Present, and Future&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We&#39;ll also have lightning talks on all three days; you will sign up for those in Durham. Details will be announced later.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you haven’t purchased your ticket yet, &lt;a href=&#34;https://ti.to/defna/djangocon-us-2024&#34;&gt;you can get them here!&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As a reminder, the in person conference runs from September 22-27 at the &lt;a href=&#34;/venue/&#34;&gt;Durham Convention Center&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We hope to see you in Durham! 🐂&lt;/p&gt;
</content
      >
    </entry>
    
    <entry>
      <title>Announcing our DjangoCon US 2024 Talks!</title>
      <link href="https://2024.djangocon.us/news/announcing-lineup/" />
      <updated>2024-08-16T18:25:39Z</updated>
      <id>https://2024.djangocon.us/news/announcing-lineup/</id>
      <content xml:lang="en" type="html"
        >&lt;p&gt;We are thrilled to present our tutorial and talk lineup!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The final talk and tutorial schedule will be announced soon. If you haven’t purchased your ticket yet, &lt;a href=&#34;https://ti.to/defna/djangocon-us-2024&#34;&gt;they’re still on sale&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Congratulations to the presenters of the tutorials and talks below!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;tutorials-(sunday%2C-september-22)&#34; tabindex=&#34;-1&#34;&gt;Tutorials (Sunday, September 22)&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Tutorials will be in person this year.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Daniele Procida (&lt;a href=&#34;https://mastodon.online/@EvilDMP&#34;&gt;mastodon&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&#34;https://vurt.org&#34;&gt;website&lt;/a&gt;) - Getting documentation done, now&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Felipe de Morais (&lt;a href=&#34;https://twitter.com/felipedemorais_&#34;&gt;twitter&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&#34;https://felipedemorais.com.br/&#34;&gt;website&lt;/a&gt;) - 🌐 Building Your First API with Django and Django Rest Framework&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Kuldeep Pisda (&lt;a href=&#34;https://twitter.com/kdpisda&#34;&gt;twitter&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&#34;https://kdpisda.in/&#34;&gt;website&lt;/a&gt;) - Efficient Django: Mastering Asynchronous Tasks with Celery, RabbitMQ, and Redis&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Lee Trout (&lt;a href=&#34;https://twitter.com/thecodewritesme&#34;&gt;twitter&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&#34;https://hachyderm.io/@leet&#34;&gt;mastodon&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&#34;http://leetrout.com&#34;&gt;website&lt;/a&gt;) - Django DevOps&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Meagen Voss (&lt;a href=&#34;https://twitter.com/meagenvoss&#34;&gt;twitter&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&#34;https://fosstodon.org/@vossisboss&#34;&gt;mastodon&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.meagenvoss.com/&#34;&gt;website&lt;/a&gt;) - How To Build More Accessible Websites with Wagtail&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Melanie Arbor  - pytest or Bust: Converting Your Django Tests to pytest&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;talks-(monday%2C-september-23-through-wednesday%2C-september-25)&#34; tabindex=&#34;-1&#34;&gt;Talks (Monday, September 23 through Wednesday, September 25)&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;All talks will be available live for those with online-only tickets. They will be posted to YouTube after the conference for free.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Adarsh Divakaran (&lt;a href=&#34;https://twitter.com/adarshd905&#34;&gt;twitter&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&#34;https://blog.adarshd.dev&#34;&gt;website&lt;/a&gt;) - Pygoat - Learn django security the hard way&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Amanda Savluchinske (&lt;a href=&#34;https://twitter.com/afsavluchinske&#34;&gt;twitter&lt;/a&gt;) - Product 101 for Techies and Tech Teams&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Avindra Fernando (&lt;a href=&#34;https://twitter.com/avindrafernando&#34;&gt;twitter&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&#34;https://taprobaneconsulting.tech/&#34;&gt;website&lt;/a&gt;) - Lessons from E2E Testing Django Web Applications&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Benjamin &amp;quot;Zags&amp;quot; Zagorsky (&lt;a href=&#34;https://zagaran.com/&#34;&gt;website&lt;/a&gt;) - Fighting Homelessness with Django&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Carlton Gibson (&lt;a href=&#34;https://fosstodon.org/@carlton&#34;&gt;mastodon&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&#34;https://noumenal.es&#34;&gt;website&lt;/a&gt;) - API Maybe: Bootstrapping a Web Application circa 2024&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Chris May (&lt;a href=&#34;https://twitter.com/_chrismay&#34;&gt;twitter&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&#34;https://fosstodon.org/@_chrismay&#34;&gt;mastodon&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&#34;https://everydaysuperpowers.dev&#34;&gt;website&lt;/a&gt;) - Choosing Wisely: SPA vs. HTMX for Your Next Web Project&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Christopher Adams (&lt;a href=&#34;https://twitter.com/adamsc64&#34;&gt;twitter&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&#34;http://christopheradams.info&#34;&gt;website&lt;/a&gt;) - A Related Matter: Optimizing your webapp by using django-debug-toolbar, select_related(), and prefetch_related()&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Daniel Ramas (&lt;a href=&#34;http://www.github.com/Daniel-Ramas&#34;&gt;website&lt;/a&gt;) - Seamless Transition: How I Converted an Existing MySQL Database to be Fully Managed by Django Migrations Framework&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Elizabeth Garrett Christensen (&lt;a href=&#34;https://twitter.com/sqlliz&#34;&gt;twitter&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&#34;https://fosstodon.org/@sqlliz&#34;&gt;mastodon&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.crunchydata.com/blog/author/elizabeth-christensen&#34;&gt;website&lt;/a&gt;) - A Guided Tour Through Postgres Internals&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Eva Nanyonga (&lt;a href=&#34;https://twitter.com/evananyonga&#34;&gt;twitter&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.linkedin.com/in/eva-nanyonga-143b6b33/&#34;&gt;website&lt;/a&gt;) - Only reliable Data: Protecting Database Integrity&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Frank Wiles (&lt;a href=&#34;https://twitter.com/fwiles&#34;&gt;twitter&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&#34;https://frankwiles.social/@frank&#34;&gt;mastodon&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.revsys.com&#34;&gt;website&lt;/a&gt;) - A Brief History of Django&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Harmony Elendu (&lt;a href=&#34;https://medium.com/harmonyelendu/&#34;&gt;website&lt;/a&gt;) - Project Management in Open Source&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Hernan Lozano (&lt;a href=&#34;https://fosstodon.org/@hernantz&#34;&gt;mastodon&lt;/a&gt;) - Reusable Django Template Components for Perfectionists with Deadlines&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Hugo Bessa (&lt;a href=&#34;https://twitter.com/hugoabessa&#34;&gt;twitter&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&#34;https://bessa.me&#34;&gt;website&lt;/a&gt;) - Django &amp;amp; Celery: A love story of async proportions&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ilerioluwakiiye Abolade - The Magic of Dependencies Installing Themselves&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Jack Linke (&lt;a href=&#34;https://social.jacklinke.com/@jack&#34;&gt;mastodon&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&#34;https://jacklinke.com/&#34;&gt;website&lt;/a&gt;) - Troubleshooting is a Lifestyle 🕶️&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Jacob Kaplan-Moss (&lt;a href=&#34;https://jacobian.org/@jacob&#34;&gt;mastodon&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&#34;https://jacobian.org/&#34;&gt;website&lt;/a&gt;) - If We Had $1,000,000: What Could The DSF Do With 4x Its Budget?&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Jessica Garson (&lt;a href=&#34;https://twitter.com/jessicagarson&#34;&gt;twitter&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&#34;https://macaw.social/@jessicagarson&#34;&gt;mastodon&lt;/a&gt;) - Introduction to OpenTelemetry with Django&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Johanan Oppong Amoateng (&lt;a href=&#34;https://twitter.com/johanan2001&#34;&gt;twitter&lt;/a&gt;) - Empowering Tertiary Students: Introducing PyClubs for Enhanced Python Skills and Community Engagement&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Josh Thomas (&lt;a href=&#34;https://joshthomas.dev/@josh&#34;&gt;mastodon&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&#34;https://joshthomas.dev&#34;&gt;website&lt;/a&gt;) - An Opinionated Guide to Modern Django Forms&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Karen Tracey (&lt;a href=&#34;https://twitter.com/km_tracey&#34;&gt;twitter&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&#34;https://fosstodon.org/@kmtracey&#34;&gt;mastodon&lt;/a&gt;) - Django + Alpine.js + htmx Ups &amp;amp; Downs&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Kasey Kelly (&lt;a href=&#34;https://twitter.com/kaseykelly&#34;&gt;twitter&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&#34;https://lincolnloop.com/&#34;&gt;website&lt;/a&gt;) - Optimizing remote work: Pull Requests, Stand-ups, and emojis&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ken Whitesell (&lt;a href=&#34;https://twitter.com/KenWhitesell&#34;&gt;twitter&lt;/a&gt;) - WebRTC with Django, Channels, HTMX, and coturn&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Lisa Ciaccio (&lt;a href=&#34;https://twitter.com/LisaChacho&#34;&gt;twitter&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.lisachacho.com&#34;&gt;website&lt;/a&gt;) - Django from a Rails Perspective&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Marc Gibbons (&lt;a href=&#34;https://mastodon.social/@marcgibbons&#34;&gt;mastodon&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&#34;https://marcgibbons.com&#34;&gt;website&lt;/a&gt;) - Finding 2.0&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Michael Riley (&lt;a href=&#34;https://twitter.com/ErriteRikez&#34;&gt;twitter&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&#34;https://michaelriley.dev&#34;&gt;website&lt;/a&gt;) - Upgrading EOL Django: A Journey from V1 to V5&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Miguel Sanda (&lt;a href=&#34;https://twitter.com/elarroba&#34;&gt;twitter&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.miguelsanda.com&#34;&gt;website&lt;/a&gt;) - Django Ledger | Uniting Developers and Accountants for Innovation.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Mohammad Ahtasham ul Hassan (&lt;a href=&#34;https://twitter.com/Iht_Malik&#34;&gt;twitter&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&#34;https://aht007.github.io/personal-portfolio/&#34;&gt;website&lt;/a&gt;) and Shafqat Farhan Ahmed  - Level Up Your Django Performance: Identifying and Taming N+1 Queries&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Paolo Melchiorre (&lt;a href=&#34;https://twitter.com/pauloxnet&#34;&gt;twitter&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&#34;https://fosstodon.org/@paulox&#34;&gt;mastodon&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.paulox.net/&#34;&gt;website&lt;/a&gt;) - Maps with Django&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Richard Ackon (&lt;a href=&#34;https://twitter.com/esquire_gh&#34;&gt;twitter&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.linkedin.com/in/richardackon/&#34;&gt;website&lt;/a&gt;) - Understanding Database Connection Management in Django&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ron Maravanyika (&lt;a href=&#34;https://twitter.com/ronn_zw&#34;&gt;twitter&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&#34;https://ronnzw.github.io/&#34;&gt;website&lt;/a&gt;) - Unlocking Performance: Benchmarking and profiling Django for Maximum Efficiency&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ryan Cheley (&lt;a href=&#34;https://mastodon.social/@ryancheley&#34;&gt;mastodon&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.ryancheley.com/&#34;&gt;website&lt;/a&gt;) - Error Culture&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ryan Hiebert (&lt;a href=&#34;https://twitter.com/ryanhiebert&#34;&gt;twitter&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&#34;https://fosstodon.org/@ryanhiebert&#34;&gt;mastodon&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&#34;http://ryanhiebert.com&#34;&gt;website&lt;/a&gt;) - Passkeys: Your password-free future&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Sage Abdullah (&lt;a href=&#34;https://twitter.com/laymonage&#34;&gt;twitter&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&#34;https://fosstodon.org/@laymonage&#34;&gt;mastodon&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&#34;https://laymonage.com&#34;&gt;website&lt;/a&gt;) - Django: the web framework that changed my life&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Samweli Mwakisambwe (&lt;a href=&#34;https://twitter.com/SamweliTwesa&#34;&gt;twitter&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&#34;https://samweli.github.io/&#34;&gt;website&lt;/a&gt;) - Open-source Python tools to visualize and analyse geospatial data.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Sarah Boyce (&lt;a href=&#34;https://mastodon.social/@sarahboyce&#34;&gt;mastodon&lt;/a&gt;) - Hidden gems of Django 5.x&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Simon Willison (&lt;a href=&#34;https://twitter.com/simonw&#34;&gt;twitter&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&#34;https://simonwillison.net/@simon&#34;&gt;mastodon&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&#34;https://simonwillison.net/&#34;&gt;website&lt;/a&gt;) - How to design and implement extensible software with plugins&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Thibaud Colas (&lt;a href=&#34;https://twitter.com/thibaud_colas&#34;&gt;twitter&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&#34;https://fosstodon.org/@thibaudcolas&#34;&gt;mastodon&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&#34;https://thib.me/&#34;&gt;website&lt;/a&gt;) - Faster, leaner, greener: 10x lower website carbon emissions&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Tim Bell (&lt;a href=&#34;https://twitter.com/timb07&#34;&gt;twitter&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&#34;https://chaos.social/@timb07&#34;&gt;mastodon&lt;/a&gt;) - Deploying Django migrations at Kraken scale&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Tim Schilling (&lt;a href=&#34;https://twitter.com/CodenameTim&#34;&gt;twitter&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&#34;https://fosstodon.org/@CodenameTim&#34;&gt;mastodon&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.better-simple.com/&#34;&gt;website&lt;/a&gt;) - You got that nice tech salary, now what?&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Vaarun Sinha (&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.linkedin.com/in/vaarun-sinha-674114230/&#34;&gt;website&lt;/a&gt;) - Streaming Video in Django | Demystified&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Vince Salvino (&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.codered.cloud/&#34;&gt;website&lt;/a&gt;) - One Thousand and One Django Sites&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Will Vincent (&lt;a href=&#34;https://learndjango.com&#34;&gt;website&lt;/a&gt;) - Django User Model: Past, Present, and Future&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Willem Van Onsem (&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.django-antipatterns.com/&#34;&gt;website&lt;/a&gt;) - path(&#39;/user/&amp;lt;user.username:user&amp;gt;/&#39;, view_profile)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Álvaro Justen (&lt;a href=&#34;https://twitter.com/turicas&#34;&gt;twitter&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&#34;https://brasil.io/&#34;&gt;website&lt;/a&gt;) - PostgreSQL Beyond Django: Strategies to Get Max Performance&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Congratulations to all our speakers!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you’d like to check out these talks and more, &lt;a href=&#34;https://ti.to/defna/djangocon-us-2024&#34;&gt;tickets are still on sale&lt;/a&gt;. Tutorials (sold separately from conference registration) are $199 each, and we will have the schedule for those up soon. We hope to see you in Durham!&lt;/p&gt;
</content
      >
    </entry>
    
    <entry>
      <title>Our New DjangoCon US 2024 Brand and Website</title>
      <link href="https://2024.djangocon.us/news/our-new-djangocon-website/" />
      <updated>2024-08-16T18:25:39Z</updated>
      <id>https://2024.djangocon.us/news/our-new-djangocon-website/</id>
      <content xml:lang="en" type="html"
        >&lt;p&gt;Fully re-built from the ground up, we are pleased to announce our brand new website and branding for DjangoCon US 2024. Every year we refresh our banding to align with our host city, but this year we decided to go a step further and re-boot our website, optimizing for contributor experience.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Why now? As noted in our &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.defna.org/announcements/2024/01/12/call-for-proposals-for-djangocon-2024-website/&#34;&gt;CFP&lt;/a&gt;, we had been using and re-skinning the same Jekyll build since 2017, and it had become increasingly cumbersome for contributors to make edits and layout changes. We hired &lt;a href=&#34;https://yupgup.com/&#34;&gt;YupGup&lt;/a&gt; to help us select a new framework, rebuild the front-end markup and CSS, and do a branding refresh. We addressed the following:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Built in 11ty, a feature-rich static site generator&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;TailwindCSS as our baseline for styles&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Made it easier to work on the website locally – no ruby needed!&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Improving the schedule with some UX enhancements.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Targeting high 90s Lighthouse scores for v1 website performance&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Introduced better tools for responsive, optimized images&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Simplified Markdown-based file formats and data.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;learn-more-about-our-design&#34; tabindex=&#34;-1&#34;&gt;Learn more about our design&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Alongside the tech stuff, we worked closely with Joni Trythall of &lt;a href=&#34;https://yupgup.com/&#34;&gt;YupGup&lt;/a&gt; to bring our second Durham edition to life, aptly named &amp;quot;Durham Doodles&amp;quot;. Here are Joni&#39;s thoughts on our process and direction:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Each year we&#39;ve collaborated with the DjangoCon US team, we kick things off with a group conversation followed by some moodboards. These moodboards are great for getting a high-level feel for a direction without investing too much time into drawing out anything overly detailed or specific. I start with some general directions in mind after our call and set out to explore the internet for screenshots to build cohesive pitches. Once a possible direction is selected, a style tile is produced for review with elements that are much more specific to the project. This enables everyone to confidently select a theme to run with.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;/assets/img/blog/durham-mood-board.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;Mood Board&#34;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;While the community is consistently friendly, welcoming, unique, and fun, some new adjectives introduced this year were unexpected, gritty, and artsy. The Cartoon Town theme direction perfectly captures and helps define the spirit of this year&#39;s upcoming event, while celebrating the heart of the community itself but also Durham. You’ll find lots of easter eggs from both throughout the design, from a seemingly misplaced crab down to the color names.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;/assets/img/blog/durham-style-tile.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;Style Tile&#34;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A significant part of this design is, of course, the doodles and characters—some new and some old favorites with a new look. Having this library of illustrations to pull from has proven to be especially valuable for these projects. The group can access all these characters and individual parts to assemble social graphics as needed and swag design really falls into place nicely—like lemur t-shirts! While a site&#39;s skeleton can be reused each year, updating these illustrations keeps the experience feeling fresh, energized, and always relevant.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;/assets/img/blog/durham-color-scheme.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;Color Scheme&#34;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;learn-more-about-the-site&#34; tabindex=&#34;-1&#34;&gt;Learn more about the site&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Considering our website serves as a primary touchpoint for attendees, speakers, sponsors, and other individuals who are curious about us, providing essential information, we took that in to consideration when it came time to design our website. Here&#39;s a closer look at the site in case you&#39;re trying to learn about the conference or looking to contribute to the site.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;1.-about-section&#34; tabindex=&#34;-1&#34;&gt;1. About section&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Our &lt;strong&gt;About&lt;/strong&gt; section is the heart of your conference website, offering visitors a clear understanding of what the event is all about. This page includes:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;/about/&#34;&gt;About DjangoCon US&lt;/a&gt;:A brief description of the conference, its theme, objectives and history&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;/tickets/&#34;&gt;Tickets&lt;/a&gt;:Information on tickets, pricing as well as our refund policy&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;/faq/&#34;&gt;FAQ&lt;/a&gt;:Information about Tickets, our Schedule, Speakers, Accessibility, Opportunity Grants and Sponsors&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;/conduct/&#34;&gt;Code of Conduct&lt;/a&gt;:Information on guidelines that are in place to insure a peaceful and and enjoyable experience&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;/public-health/&#34;&gt;Public Health Policy&lt;/a&gt;:Information on DjangoCon US 2024&#39;s public health policy&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;/opportunity-grants/&#34;&gt;Opportunity Grants&lt;/a&gt;: Information regarding grants: who can get it and what it means&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;/visas/&#34;&gt;Visa Support&lt;/a&gt;: Information for international travelers&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;/organizers/&#34;&gt;Organizers&lt;/a&gt;: Details about the organizing committee / organization&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;2.-venue-page&#34; tabindex=&#34;-1&#34;&gt;2. Venue page&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Our &lt;a href=&#34;/venue/&#34;&gt;Venue page&lt;/a&gt; highlights all the important information of Durham, North Carolina. It includes:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Location Details: The exact address of the venue, along with a map for easy navigation&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Accessibility: Information on how to reach the venue by various modes of transport&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Accommodation Options: Recommendations for nearby hotels and accommodations&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Restaurants and local attractions are available in the area&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;3.-speaking-section&#34; tabindex=&#34;-1&#34;&gt;3. Speaking section&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The &lt;strong&gt;Speaking&lt;/strong&gt; section features information for both prospective and selected speakers. If your talk is selected, we highly recommend reviewing the &lt;a href=&#34;/speaking/speaker-resources/&#34;&gt;Speaker Resources&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;/speaking/&#34;&gt;Speaking at DjangoCon US&lt;/a&gt;: Information regarding speaking benefits, talk formats, CFP, travel assistance and gear reimbursement&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;/speaking/speaker-resources/&#34;&gt;Speaker Resources&lt;/a&gt;: Helpful information and guidelines for your talk and slides&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;4.-sponsors-section&#34; tabindex=&#34;-1&#34;&gt;4. Sponsors section&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Sponsors play a crucial role in the success of DjangoCon US. The Sponsors section showcases sponsors on our website acknowledging their support of DjangoCon US and the broader Django community.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;/sponsors/&#34;&gt;Our Sponsors&lt;/a&gt;: A list of all sponsors, including their logo, a brief description of their business and a link to their website&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;/sponsors/information/&#34;&gt;Sponsorship Prospectus&lt;/a&gt;: Want to sponsor DjangoCon US? Fantastic, check this page out for how to do that and learn about the benefits of sponsoring DjangoCon US&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;5.-news-page&#34; tabindex=&#34;-1&#34;&gt;5. News page&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The &lt;a href=&#34;/news/&#34;&gt;News page&lt;/a&gt; keeps people informed with the latest updates and blog posts. Some examples of what you&#39;ll find there are updates on new speakers, important deadlines, and other critical information.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;want-to-contribute%3F&#34; tabindex=&#34;-1&#34;&gt;Want to contribute?&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Feel free to take a look around, browse our codebase or &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/djangocon/2024.djangocon.us/issues&#34;&gt;file an issue&lt;/a&gt; if you find a bug! As always, everything is done in the open on &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/djangocon/2024.djangocon.us&#34;&gt;GitHub&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
</content
      >
    </entry>
    
    <entry>
      <title>Early-bird tickets now on sale!</title>
      <link href="https://2024.djangocon.us/news/early-bird-tickets-on-sale/" />
      <updated>2024-08-16T18:25:39Z</updated>
      <id>https://2024.djangocon.us/news/early-bird-tickets-on-sale/</id>
      <content xml:lang="en" type="html"
        >&lt;h2 id=&#34;hey-django-fans!-%F0%9F%91%8B&#34; tabindex=&#34;-1&#34;&gt;Hey Django fans! 👋&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Tickets for DjangoCon US 2024 in Durham, NC are now on sale.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;🐂 &lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://ti.to/defna/djangocon-us-2024&#34;&gt;Buy yours today!&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; 🐂&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This year we have limited early-bird pricing for individual tickets and corporate tickets. We lowered Individual ticket prices to make the conference more accessible and more affordable so that anyone paying to attend DjangoCon US out of their own pocket can more easily do so.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Early-bird individual: $339 (full price: $499)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Early-bird corporate: $699 (full price: $799)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The early-bird pricing will only be available through the month of May.&lt;/strong&gt; Starting June 1st, tickets will be available at their full price.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Purchasing your tickets early not only saves you money, but it also helps organizers prepare for the conference. Besides the obvious factors of knowing how many meals to order and what size projector screens we&#39;ll need, it offsets the early payments made to vendors and gives us confidence to enhance and expand the conference experience. If you&#39;re able to commit to attending DjangoCon US early, that&#39;s fantastic. If you need more time, don&#39;t worry; that works for us too.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;And lastly, if you&#39;re ecstatic about the idea of attending DjangoCon US but need financial assistance to do so, our &lt;a href=&#34;/opportunity-grants/&#34;&gt;Opportunity Grant CFP&lt;/a&gt; is open until April 29th.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We can’t wait to see you in Durham!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;🐂 &lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://ti.to/defna/djangocon-us-2024&#34;&gt;Buy your ticket here!&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; 🐂&lt;/p&gt;
</content
      >
    </entry>
    
    <entry>
      <title>Heads Up! End of our Opportunity Grants is coming up!</title>
      <link href="https://2024.djangocon.us/news/opportunity-grant-last-call/" />
      <updated>2024-08-16T18:25:39Z</updated>
      <id>https://2024.djangocon.us/news/opportunity-grant-last-call/</id>
      <content xml:lang="en" type="html"
        >&lt;h2 id=&#34;hey-django-lovers%2C&#34; tabindex=&#34;-1&#34;&gt;Hey Django lovers,&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;UPDATE&lt;/strong&gt;: The application window has been extended to Monday, April 29th at Noon EDT!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Here to remind you that the &lt;a href=&#34;https://2024.djangocon.us/opportunity-grants/&#34;&gt;opportunity grants&lt;/a&gt; will be closing on April 29, 2024 at &lt;a href=&#34;https://time.is/1200PM_29_Apr_2024_in_New_York?DjangoCon_US_2024_CFP_closes&#34;&gt;12 PM EDT&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you haven&#39;t already applied, make sure to fill the &lt;a href=&#34;https://forms.gle/Pi12J6vFQHq2CSAy5&#34;&gt;opportunity grant application form&lt;/a&gt; soon.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What are opportunity grants?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;They are grants to encourage and facilitate the participation of those who otherwise might not be able to attend the conference. They can be used for conference-related expenses like travel, lodging, etc.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Who will be eligible to receive an opportunity grant?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Anyone, anyone who needs financial support attending our conference.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;When will I find out whether I’ve received an opportunity grant?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;You will be notified by &lt;strong&gt;June 14, 2024&lt;/strong&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you would like more information on opportunity grants, click &lt;a href=&#34;https://2024.djangocon.us/opportunity-grants/&#34;&gt;here&lt;/a&gt; to go to the grants information page.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Happy Scrolling!&lt;/p&gt;
</content
      >
    </entry>
    
    <entry>
      <title>Don't Miss Out: Last Call for DjangoCon US 2024 Talk Proposals!</title>
      <link href="https://2024.djangocon.us/news/cfp-last-call/" />
      <updated>2024-08-16T18:25:39Z</updated>
      <id>https://2024.djangocon.us/news/cfp-last-call/</id>
      <content xml:lang="en" type="html"
        >&lt;p&gt;Hey Django enthusiasts!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;UPDATE&lt;/strong&gt;: The CFP has been extended to Monday, April 29th at Noon EDT!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Have you submitted your talk or tutorial for DjangoCon US 2024, in beautiful Durham, North Carolina, USA?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Time flies, and we&#39;re fast approaching the deadline (April 29, 2024 at &lt;a href=&#34;https://time.is/1200PM_29_Apr_2024_in_New_York?DjangoCon_US_2024_CFP_closes&#34;&gt;12 PM EDT&lt;/a&gt;) for DjangoCon US 2024 &lt;a href=&#34;https://pretalx.com/djangocon-us-2024/cfp&#34;&gt;Call for Proposals (CFP)&lt;/a&gt;. If you&#39;ve been pondering sharing your Django journey, showcasing your innovative projects, or imparting your expertise to fellow developers, now is the perfect moment to seize the opportunity!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Here&#39;s why you should take action and submit your proposals before the clock runs out:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Share Your Knowledge:&lt;/strong&gt; DjangoCon US isn&#39;t just a conference; it&#39;s a platform for sharing insights, discoveries, and lessons learned. Your unique experiences could be just what someone else needs to overcome a hurdle or spark a new idea.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Join the Community:&lt;/strong&gt; DjangoCon US isn&#39;t just about talks; it&#39;s about building connections. By presenting at the conference, you become an integral part of the vibrant Django community, exchanging ideas, and forging new friendships with like-minded developers.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Boost Your Profile:&lt;/strong&gt; Whether you&#39;re a seasoned speaker or a first-time presenter, DjangoCon US offers a valuable opportunity to elevate your profile in the tech industry. Showcase your expertise, gain visibility, and enhance your professional credibility among peers and potential employers.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Contribute to Diversity:&lt;/strong&gt; DjangoCon US values diversity and inclusion. Your perspective matters, and by sharing your voice, you contribute to creating a more inclusive and representative tech community.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Submitting a proposal is easy! Just head over to the DjangoCon US website, fill out the submission form, and share your compelling idea with us. Whether it&#39;s a deep dive into a technical topic, a case study of your latest project, or a discussion on the future of Django, we want to hear from you.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Remember, the deadline for CFP submissions is fast approaching, so don&#39;t wait until the last minute. Take this opportunity to inspire, educate, and connect with your fellow Django enthusiasts at DjangoCon US 2024!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;See you at the conference!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you have questions feel free &lt;a href=&#34;mailto:hello@djangocon.us&#34;&gt;to contact us&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
</content
      >
    </entry>
    
    <entry>
      <title>Announcing Call for Community Reviewers</title>
      <link href="https://2024.djangocon.us/news/call-for-community-reviewers/" />
      <updated>2024-08-16T18:25:39Z</updated>
      <id>https://2024.djangocon.us/news/call-for-community-reviewers/</id>
      <content xml:lang="en" type="html"
        >&lt;p&gt;The &lt;a href=&#34;/speaking/&#34;&gt;call for proposals for DjangoCon US 2024&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br&gt;
is open, and we would love to have you (yes, you!) help us select our talks and tutorials&lt;br&gt;
this year. We strive to create a schedule that appeals to the wider community, and the best&lt;br&gt;
way for us to do that is by having members of said community vote for the talks you’d like&lt;br&gt;
to see. If you are interested in guiding the 2024 program, this is your chance!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We welcome reviewers with all levels of experience, including those who are brand&lt;br&gt;
new to the community. You don’t need to be a Django expert, a previous reviewer,&lt;br&gt;
or a frequent DjangoCon US attendee. It takes people of all backgrounds to make&lt;br&gt;
a program that appeals to everyone!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you are interested in volunteering as a community reviewer, please email&lt;br&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;mailto:program@djangocon.us&#34;&gt;program@djangocon.us&lt;/a&gt;. Please note, we can&lt;br&gt;
only grant access to around 30 community reviewers. We will grant access&lt;br&gt;
on a first-come, first-served basis.&lt;/p&gt;
</content
      >
    </entry>
    
    <entry>
      <title>Call for Volunteers: DjangoCon US 2024</title>
      <link href="https://2024.djangocon.us/news/call-for-2024-volunteers/" />
      <updated>2024-08-16T18:25:39Z</updated>
      <id>https://2024.djangocon.us/news/call-for-2024-volunteers/</id>
      <content xml:lang="en" type="html"
        >&lt;p&gt;Organizing DjangoCon US 2024 has begun! We need organizers to help make DjangoCon US 2024 the best it can be.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We have some &lt;a href=&#34;https://djangocon.github.io/djangocon-us-docs/&#34;&gt;documentation about the various roles&lt;/a&gt;, but here&#39;s a quick overview of the teams at DjangoCon US.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The DEFNA board will not leave you stranded; we have a lot of documentation to help you on your way, including rough checklists of tasks needed for each team.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Ideally, all committees will have a chair and co-chair to allow for one or the other to take vacations, handle day job duties, and so forth. This list is by no means comprehensive, but it should hopefully give you an idea of what each committee is responsible for.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;conference-leadership&#34; tabindex=&#34;-1&#34;&gt;Conference Leadership&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The conference chair and co-chair lead the conference, including coordinating between teams and making executive decisions (including approaching the DEFNA board when applicable). Expect to be in meetings with the venue and online conference provider, weekly organizer check-ins, monthly reports to the DEFNA board, and lots of questions on Slack. You&#39;ll also lead the volunteer kickoff meetings in early 2024 (ideally mid-to-late January) and recruit organizers as you see fit. You&#39;ll need to recommend an online conference provider to the DEFNA board (might be part of a sponsorship deal).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;At the conference, you&#39;ll be making speeches at the start of each day and the end-of-conference wrap-up in addition to coordinating setup, teardown, and everything in between.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;These two roles have the highest time commitment and the most visibility. If you want to help people get things done and get up on stage, these are the roles for you.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;program-committee&#34; tabindex=&#34;-1&#34;&gt;Program Committee&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Size: 2-4&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The program committee is responsible for making sure that the schedule of tutorials and talks is the best it can be.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;pre-conference-responsibilities&#34; tabindex=&#34;-1&#34;&gt;Pre-conference responsibilities&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Start the call for proposals process (opened in March 2024, closes April 29)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Coordinate with the Opportunity Grants team to schedule the opening and closing of the CFP&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Publish blog posts announcing the CFP, speaker mentors, and speaker resources&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Recruit keynote speakers (the DEFNA board will offer suggestions, but if you have a message you&#39;d like the keynotes to send, you have lots of latitude here, but keep in mind conference diversity goals)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Recruit speaker mentors (start with the 2019, 2021, and 2022 reviewers and bring in more as you like)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Review proposals as they come in for anonymization (ideally, recruit one member of the program committee who will not be reviewing talks to do the anonymization before opening talks for review)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Recruit talk reviewers (the DEFNA board will send you the 2023 reviewers, but more reviewers are encouraged, especially from diverse backgrounds). There will likely be over 100 submissions, so having more reviewers lessens the load for individual talks&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Decide on any tweaks to the format (Spanish-language talks? Keep the Deep Dive Day? This is your chance to put your mark on the program)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Review talks&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Once reviews are completed, de-anonymize talks and filter for duplicate speakers, multiple speakers from the same organization, diversity goals, overlapping topics, and more&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Select the best talks (where &amp;quot;best&amp;quot; is extremely subjective; we have documentation on things we look for in good proposals); you&#39;re not strictly bound to pick the highest scoring talks, so you have some leeway&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Coordinate with the Opportunity Grants team to send them a list of accepted speakers so they can prioritize them for awards&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Coordinate with the OG team to notify speakers in waves (ideally completed by July 1)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Build a schedule (ideally by July 15)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Publish blog posts announcing speakers and keynotes (ideally by August 15)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Update schedules based on speakers&#39; needs&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Coordinate with the DEFNA board to approve reimbursement requests&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Generate cue sheets for session chairs and speaker mentors&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Review online talks for Code of Conduct compliance&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Recruit backup speakers in case of speakers having to back out (visa issues, illness, etc.)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Work with the social events team to arrange a speaker appreciation dinner&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Generate spreadsheets in multiple formats to make other teams&#39; lives easier&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;at-conference-responsibilities&#34; tabindex=&#34;-1&#34;&gt;At-conference responsibilities&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Work with registration desk to make sure that all speakers show up&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Work with session managers (other organizers) to ensure distribution of cue sheets and speaker gifts&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Check with tutorial speakers to make sure they have everything they need&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;opportunity-grants-committee&#34; tabindex=&#34;-1&#34;&gt;Opportunity Grants Committee&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Size: 2 (plus reviewers)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The OG committee is responsible for obtaining grants from the DSF and PSF and awarding grants to people who will best use them, prioritizing speakers, first time attendees, and people from underrepresented and/or historically disadvantaged groups.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;pre-conference-responsibilities-1&#34; tabindex=&#34;-1&#34;&gt;Pre-conference responsibilities&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Start call for grants process (concurrent with CFP)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Publish blog posts announcing the grant process&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Request grants from the Django Software Foundation and Python Software Foundation (the DEFNA board will help you fill out the forms)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Recruit grant reviewers (other organizers and DEFNA members are happy to help)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Review submissions&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Coordinate with the program team about grants to speakers&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Notify grant recipients in waves (concurrent with program notifications)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Communicate with recipients on how to get reimbursed (we&#39;ll have templates)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Give DEFNA a list of recipients and amounts&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Approve reimbursements as requests come in&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Coordinate with the visa (community) team as needed to approve invitation letter requests&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Write a transparency report giving a high-level overview of how the grants were awarded&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;at-conference-responsibilities-1&#34; tabindex=&#34;-1&#34;&gt;At-conference responsibilities&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Answer questions from grant recipients and the DEFNA board&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;community-team&#34; tabindex=&#34;-1&#34;&gt;Community Team&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Size: 2-4&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;pre-conference-responsibilities-2&#34; tabindex=&#34;-1&#34;&gt;Pre-conference responsibilities&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Schedule orientation&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Arrange childcare and lactation room&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Coordinate visa applications&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Improve accessibility of the venue and conference as a whole&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;at-conference-responsibilities-2&#34; tabindex=&#34;-1&#34;&gt;At-conference responsibilities&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Post-sign-ups for the lactation room and distribute keys as needed&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Collect receipts for childcare reimbursement&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;sponsorship-committee&#34; tabindex=&#34;-1&#34;&gt;Sponsorship Committee&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Size: 2-4&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The sponsorship committee recruits sponsors which helps offset the cost of running DCUS.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;pre-conference-responsibilities-3&#34; tabindex=&#34;-1&#34;&gt;Pre-conference responsibilities&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Create and announce sponsorship prospectus (we have templates, and DEFNA will help with specifics)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Recruit sponsors&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Coordinate contract signing with DEFNA&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Consider awarding community sponsorships (non-financial) to other non-profit Python conferences and related communities (local Python meetups near the conference will love the exposure)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Coordinate shipping of sponsor swag for the swag bag&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Lay out sponsor tables (on a venue map)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Work with sponsor chair/co-chair to handle sponsor shout-outs if needed&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Order banners to go behind the speakers on stage&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;at-conference-responsibilities-3&#34; tabindex=&#34;-1&#34;&gt;At-conference responsibilities&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Direct sponsors to their booths/tables and swag&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ensure that booths are reserved for sponsors who have reserved a booth, and are not open for others&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Field complaints/questions from sponsors&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;code-of-conduct-committee&#34; tabindex=&#34;-1&#34;&gt;Code of Conduct Committee&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Size: 4-6&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The CoC committee suggests improvements to the CoC and investigates reports. This is the heart of the conference because, without the CoC, we wouldn&#39;t have the welcoming environment that we have at DCUS.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;pre-conference-responsibilities-4&#34; tabindex=&#34;-1&#34;&gt;Pre-conference responsibilities&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Suggest modifications/improvements to the CoC&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Assist program committee with pre-conference review of recorded online talks&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;at-conference-responsibilities-4&#34; tabindex=&#34;-1&#34;&gt;At-conference responsibilities&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Field reports and investigate them, including recommending actions to the DEFNA board&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Follow up on reports, including conversations with both reporters and those who have been reported, and facilitate the appropriate response&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Write a CoC transparency report to recap reports (heavily anonymized) and actions taken&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;social-events-committee&#34; tabindex=&#34;-1&#34;&gt;Social Events Committee&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Size: 2-3&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The social events committee is responsible for scheduling the &amp;quot;after-hours&amp;quot; events at DCUS to give people chances to socialize and unwind after a long day of talks.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;pre-conference-responsibilities-5&#34; tabindex=&#34;-1&#34;&gt;Pre-conference responsibilities&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Find a venue for the speaker appreciation dinner and coordinate contract signing with DEFNA&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Plan opening reception (if sponsored, this will become a bigger event compared to previous years)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Plan any other fun events like board game night&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;at-conference-responsibilities-5&#34; tabindex=&#34;-1&#34;&gt;At-conference responsibilities&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Work with the venue on any work needed for social events&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;venue-committee&#34; tabindex=&#34;-1&#34;&gt;Venue Committee&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Size: 1-2&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The venue committee is responsible for coordinating plans between the other organizing teams and the venue(s).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;pre-conference-responsibilities-6&#34; tabindex=&#34;-1&#34;&gt;Pre-conference responsibilities&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Work with the event venue to select and lay out talk, tutorial, and sprint rooms&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Lay out the extra rooms needed for the conference (lactation room, quiet room, organizers room, speaker green room, lunch/break areas)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Work with event venue and DEFNA to select catering menus (and providers if we&#39;re not contractually obligated to use one)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Work with the hotel to coordinate room blocks&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Work with the venue to plan logistics (sponsor gear shipping, signage, etc.)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Allocate reward rooms in coordination with the DEFNA board&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Order supplies for restroom stocking&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;at-conference-responsibilities-6&#34; tabindex=&#34;-1&#34;&gt;At-conference responsibilities&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Review room guest list against ticket list to claim reward nights&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Handle any last-minute requests from vendors/sponsors/organizers/etc.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Notify venue staff of any needs (bathroom cleanliness, meals to accommodate special diets, etc.)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;online-committee&#34; tabindex=&#34;-1&#34;&gt;Online Committee&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Size: 2-3&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;during-conference-responsibilities&#34; tabindex=&#34;-1&#34;&gt;During-conference responsibilities&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Increase online engagement during the conference&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Investigate online lightning talks&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;audio%2Fvideo-(a%2Fv)-committee&#34; tabindex=&#34;-1&#34;&gt;Audio/Video (A/V) Committee&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Size: 2-3&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The A/V committee is responsible for making everything look good. They handle coordination between the on-site crew, the online streaming platform, and the post-conference processing teams and upload the results to YouTube after the conference.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;pre-conference-responsibilities-7&#34; tabindex=&#34;-1&#34;&gt;Pre-conference responsibilities&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Select on-site video production crew&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Select post-conference processing crew&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Coordinate both of the above teams with the online platform&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Work with the venue team to ensure high-speed wired internet access to the on-site video crew&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Transfer pre-recorded talks to the post-conference processing crew and then the online conference provider&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Procure a wide variety of dongles for presenters to hook their laptops up to the projectors&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Procure projectors and screens if the venue doesn&#39;t already have them, including one for the green room so speakers can test their setup&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;at-conference-responsibilities-7&#34; tabindex=&#34;-1&#34;&gt;At-conference responsibilities&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Help on-site crew set up equipment and ensure streaming works&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Get dongles to the right rooms as needed&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Help keynote speakers get presentation mode working if needed&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Answer lots and lots of questions&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;swag-committee&#34; tabindex=&#34;-1&#34;&gt;Swag Committee&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Size: 1-2&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The swag committee is responsible for everything speakers and attendees take home from the conference (aside from knowledge!).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;pre-conference-responsibilities-8&#34; tabindex=&#34;-1&#34;&gt;Pre-conference responsibilities&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Design and order attendee t-shirts (with sponsor logos)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Design and order swag bags (with sponsor logos)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Design and order speaker gifts&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Design and order DCUS-branded swag (stickers/magnets/etc.)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Order masks and COVID tests (if needed)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Order lanyards, badges, and badge flags&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;at-conference-responsibilities-8&#34; tabindex=&#34;-1&#34;&gt;At-conference responsibilities&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Recruit volunteers to stuff swag bags on Sunday afternoon&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Get T-shirts and swag bags to the registration desk&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Get speaker gifts to the program team for distribution&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;volunteer-committee&#34; tabindex=&#34;-1&#34;&gt;Volunteer Committee&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Size: 2&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The volunteer committee is responsible for cultivating new volunteers, who can become organizers in future years.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;pre-conference-responsibilities-9&#34; tabindex=&#34;-1&#34;&gt;Pre-conference responsibilities&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Determine what roles need on-site volunteer support (session chairs, session managers, registration desk, etc.)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Set up sign-up for on-site volunteers and online volunteers (moderators/cheerleaders)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Draft announcements for calls for volunteers&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;at-conference-responsibilities-9&#34; tabindex=&#34;-1&#34;&gt;At-conference responsibilities&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Tell volunteers where to go&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Give volunteers tools to succeed&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;communications-committee&#34; tabindex=&#34;-1&#34;&gt;Communications Committee&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Size: 2-4&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The communications committee is responsible for getting the word out about DCUS.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This team manages the various DCUS social network feeds, including Twitter, Mastodon, Bluesky, Instagram, LinkedIn, and more. This team also edits and posts blogs on the DCUS main page and coordinates bulk emails to ticketholders to remind them about the conference as it approaches.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;pre-conference-responsibilities-10&#34; tabindex=&#34;-1&#34;&gt;Pre-conference responsibilities&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Publish announcements and reminders on social media, the conference blog, and more (Django News, Python Community News, etc.)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Send a copy to the Django Software Foundation to get major news events on the Django blog&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Review, edit, and suggest copy for the other teams&#39; announcements&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Tweet. Lots of tweeting.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Select an &amp;quot;official emoji&amp;quot; for the conference (typically suggested by the design package for the year&#39;s website)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Boost and retweet speakers and organizers talking about the conference&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Schedule tweets announcing talks and events&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;at-conference-responsibilities-10&#34; tabindex=&#34;-1&#34;&gt;At-conference responsibilities&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Pay attention to the &lt;code&gt;#djangocon&lt;/code&gt; topic on social media and mentions to &lt;code&gt;@djangocon&lt;/code&gt; on various social networks&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Boost speakers and organizers&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Answer questions as they come up&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Run the &lt;code&gt;#help-desk&lt;/code&gt; channel on the conference attendee slack&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;website-committee&#34; tabindex=&#34;-1&#34;&gt;Website Committee&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Size: 2-3&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The website committee is responsible for updating the website as the conference transitions through phases (CFP coming soon, CFP open, CFP closed, schedule released, hotel block closed, conference over, etc.), reviewing pull requests, and adding content (e.g. new sponsors). This requires the most coding of any team aside from maybe the program team.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;pre-conference-responsibilities-11&#34; tabindex=&#34;-1&#34;&gt;Pre-conference responsibilities&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Update static pages for CFP status&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Update static pages for venue information&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Review pull requests from other teams&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Add sponsors as directed by the sponsorship team&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;automation-team&#34; tabindex=&#34;-1&#34;&gt;Automation Team&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This team is more free-flowing and writes scripts to make teams&#39; lives easier. Responsibilities vary based on the year, and if you have ideas for special projects for the future, have at it!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;sprints-team&#34; tabindex=&#34;-1&#34;&gt;Sprints Team&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Size: 2-4&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;pre-conference-responsibilities-12&#34; tabindex=&#34;-1&#34;&gt;Pre-conference responsibilities&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Write blog posts announcing sprints&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Invite people to launch special sessions (e.g. Carlton&#39;s &lt;a href=&#34;https://2022.djangocon.us/sprints/getting-started-contributing-to-django/&#34;&gt;&amp;quot;Getting Started Contributing to Django&amp;quot;&lt;/a&gt;)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ensure we have signage and power equipment&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;at-conference-responsibilities-11&#34; tabindex=&#34;-1&#34;&gt;At-conference responsibilities&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Coordinate help desk&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Direct people to lunches and breaks&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;wrap-up&#34; tabindex=&#34;-1&#34;&gt;Wrap-up&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;To sign up for any of the teams (or just say &amp;quot;Put me to work&amp;quot;), send an email to &lt;a href=&#34;mailto:hello@djangocon.us&#34;&gt;hello@djangocon.us&lt;/a&gt; and we&#39;ll add you to our organizer Slack instance and invite you to our fortnightly organizer catch-up meetings. We would love to have you! You do not have to have previous organizing experience (although we might prefer it for some of the leadership roles).&lt;/p&gt;
</content
      >
    </entry>
    
    <entry>
      <title>What are the Benefits of Speaking at DjangoCon US?</title>
      <link href="https://2024.djangocon.us/news/benefits-of-speaking-djangocon/" />
      <updated>2024-08-16T18:25:39Z</updated>
      <id>https://2024.djangocon.us/news/benefits-of-speaking-djangocon/</id>
      <content xml:lang="en" type="html"
        >&lt;p&gt;The DjangoCon US team would like to make sure you are aware of some of the benefits of giving a talk at DjangoCon US 2024.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;benefits-you-will-receive-for-being-a-presenter%3A&#34; tabindex=&#34;-1&#34;&gt;Benefits you will receive for being a presenter:&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;FREE! Ticket to DjancoCon US 2024.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Up to $500 in travel cost reimbursement!&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;A professionally produced video of your talk will be published on our YouTube channel.&lt;/strong&gt; (You may opt out of this.)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Professional photographer on hand to photograph your talk.&lt;/strong&gt; (Also optional.)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;still-on-the-fence-deciding-if-you-want-to-give-a-talk-or-not%3F&#34; tabindex=&#34;-1&#34;&gt;Still on the fence deciding if you want to give a talk or not?&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Building your reputation:&lt;/strong&gt; Presenting at DjangoCon US can establish you as an expert in the Django community, raising your profile and building your reputation.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Networking:&lt;/strong&gt; Speaking at DjangoCon US provides an opportunity to connect with other developers, designers, and enthusiasts in the Django community, allowing you to expand your network and make new connections.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Career advancement:&lt;/strong&gt; Speaking at DjangoCon US can help you advance your career by demonstrating your knowledge and expertise, which can lead to new job opportunities or promotions.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Feedback and learning:&lt;/strong&gt; Presenting at DjangoCon US gives you the opportunity to receive feedback from your peers, which helps you improve your skills and knowledge.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Giving back to the community:&lt;/strong&gt; By sharing your knowledge and experience with others at DjangoCon US, you are contributing to the growth and development of the Django community, which is a rewarding experience in itself.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Travel and conference experience:&lt;/strong&gt; Speaking at DjangoCon US includes travel to interesting locations, attending the conference to learn from other presenters, and give you a valuable conference experience that broadens your horizons.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;need-topic-ideas%3F&#34; tabindex=&#34;-1&#34;&gt;Need Topic Ideas?&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We&#39;ve had organizers create lists of talk ideas they&#39;d like to see:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://katherinemichel.github.io/portfolio/djangocon-us-2024-topics-inspiration-list.html&#34;&gt;Kati&#39;s list&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://winstel.dev/2024/03/01/talk-ideas-for-dcus-24/&#34;&gt;Drew&#39;s list&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;all-right%2C-you&#39;ve-convinced-me.-how-do-i-submit%3F&#34; tabindex=&#34;-1&#34;&gt;All right, you&#39;ve convinced me. How do I submit?&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Go to the &lt;a href=&#34;/speaking/&#34;&gt;Speaking page&lt;/a&gt; to see all the details.&lt;/p&gt;
</content
      >
    </entry>
    
    <entry>
      <title>The Call for Proposals for DjangoCon US 2024 Is Now Open!</title>
      <link href="https://2024.djangocon.us/news/announcing-call-for-proposals/" />
      <updated>2024-08-16T18:25:39Z</updated>
      <id>https://2024.djangocon.us/news/announcing-call-for-proposals/</id>
      <content xml:lang="en" type="html"
        >&lt;p&gt;We are excited that DjangoCon US 2024 is now open for talk submissions: &lt;a href=&#34;https://pretalx.com/djangocon-us-2024/cfp&#34;&gt;call for proposals&lt;/a&gt;! The deadline for submissions is April 24th, 2024 at &lt;a href=&#34;https://time.is/1200PM_24_April_2024_in_Durham,_United_States?DjangoCon_US_CFP_Closes&#34;&gt;Noon EDT&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We invite you to submit your proposal no matter your background or experience level with Django. Proposals can be from a wide range of topics; non-Django and community topics are welcome. You can look at our &lt;a href=&#34;https://2023.djangocon.us/talks/&#34;&gt;talk schedule&lt;/a&gt; from last year for reference.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We fancy first-timers! If you haven’t spoken at a conference or given a tutorial before, this is your invitation to do so. Don’t let the idea that you’re not famous or an expert stop you from submitting. It certainly won’t stop us from selecting your talk or tutorial and it won’t stop the audience from enjoying it! Please contact one of our amazing &lt;a href=&#34;https://2024.djangocon.us/speaking/speaker-resources/&#34;&gt;speaker mentors&lt;/a&gt; to help you on your way.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Plus there are perks! Presenters get free admission to DjangoCon US! Grants to assist with your travel and lodging expenses are available as well. Fill out the &lt;a href=&#34;https://forms.gle/Pi12J6vFQHq2CSAy5&#34;&gt;Opportunity Grants&lt;/a&gt; form by April 24th, 2024. Decision notifications will be sent by June 14, 2024.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;For more information on talk and tutorial formats, please check out our &lt;a href=&#34;https://2024.djangocon.us/speaking/&#34;&gt;speaker information page&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We want everyone attending DjangoCon US to feel safe, welcome, and included. To that end, we have a &lt;a href=&#34;https://2024.djangocon.us/conduct/&#34;&gt;Code of Conduct&lt;/a&gt; for all speakers and attendees.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you have questions feel free &lt;a href=&#34;mailto:hello@djangocon.us&#34;&gt;to contact us&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We look forward to your proposals!&lt;/p&gt;
</content
      >
    </entry>
    
    <entry>
      <title>Code, test, ship it! DjangoCon US 2024 has been announced!</title>
      <link href="https://2024.djangocon.us/news/announcing-djangocon-us-2024/" />
      <updated>2024-08-16T18:25:39Z</updated>
      <id>https://2024.djangocon.us/news/announcing-djangocon-us-2024/</id>
      <content xml:lang="en" type="html"
        >&lt;p&gt;Hello everyone, we have our dates! September 22nd-27th.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The conference will have tutorials on Sunday, September 22nd, talks from Monday, September 23rd through Wednesday, September 25th, and sprints on Thursday and Friday, September 26th and 27th, 2024.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;September 22: Tutorials (Additional fee)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;September 23-25: Talks&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;September 26-27: Sprints&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This year, our venue will again be the Durham Convention Center in Durham, NC.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Please start getting your submissions for talks and tutorials ready. We will be posting updates when our Opportunity Grants and speaking CFP open.&lt;br&gt;
We look forward to seeing everyone for another great year at DjangoCon US!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Keep in touch on &lt;a href=&#34;https://twitter.com/djangocon&#34;&gt;Twitter/X&lt;/a&gt; or &lt;a href=&#34;https://fosstodon.org/@djangocon&#34;&gt;Mastodon&lt;/a&gt; for more announcements along the way!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;DjangoCon US Organizers 🐂&lt;/p&gt;
</content
      >
    </entry>
</feed>
